

AKIS GAZEPIDIS

DATA SCIENTIST

PROFILE

Data Scientist with experience in information extraction techniques used on do cuments, scraping data through internet and training of machine learning models. My passion is to accelerate internal company processes and lead to data-driven decisions.

CONTACT

6986777430

<u>akisgazepidis@gmail.com</u>

in <u>linkedin.com/in/akisgazepidis</u>

<u>akisgazepidis.github.io/Akis_Gazepidis</u>

Peristeri, Athens, 12137, Greece

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- · Critical Thinking
- Adaptability
- Team Working

HARD SKILLS

- Python
- Snowflake
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- PowerBi
- Databricks
- Excel

EXPERIENCE

DATA ENGINEERING CONSULTANT

D-ONE

Apr 2023- Present

- Transfer tables from Azure SQL server in Snowflake.
- Build, test and deploy models using dbt library.
- · Assure of data quality in tables.
- · Create PowerBi reports.

DATA SCIENTIST

Generali

Jan 2022- Apr 2023

- Integrate Bitbucket version control system in development.
- · Consolidate data with the use of APIs.
- Create RPA bots so as to automate consuming processes.
- Integrate OCR, Machine Vision & Machine Learning fields to RPA bots.

DATA SCIENTIST

Purposeful in Colaboration with Big Blue Academy

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

- Collect publication patents through Google's BigQuery.
- Analyze texts with Natural Language Process (NLP).
- Conduct topic modeling analysis using Latent Dirichlet Allocation. (LDA)

LANGUAGES

Greek - Native

English - ILTES 6.5

PORTFOLIO

Optimization of Titan's Mill

<u>Deep Learning - loan prediction</u>

<u>Classcentral scraper</u>

Tweeter users analysis

JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST

Big Blue Data Academy

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

- Web scraping with Beautiful Soup, Requests & Selenium.
- Consolidate various data sources using Pandas & JSON.
- · Data visualization using Plotly, Dash, Power BI.
- Recommendation System with Natural Language Process (NLP) & TFIDF

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

University of Piraeus - Statistics

2011 - 2020

MASTER OF SCIENCE

American College of Greece - Data Science

2022 - Present

DATA SCIENCE BOOTCAMP 500 HOURS HANDS-ON

Big Blue Data Academy

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

- Databases (SQL, MongoDB) , APIs & Web Scraping
- EDA & Data Cleaning (Pandas, Numpy, Regex)
- Big Data (PySpark) & Cloud Computing (Amazon Web Services)
- Machine Learning (Scikit Learn) & Deep Learning (Keras)
- · Visualization (Matplotlib, Seaborn, Dash, PowerBi)
- · Communication & Presentation skills

DATA SCIENCE WORKSHOP 100 HOURS HANDS-ON

Regeneration Academy by TITAN- Code. Hub

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021